Um overall really pleased. It was
awesome to see our field goal operation.
Meas hitting a couple big field goals. I
think that's going to serve us really
well and um you know it was a good
complete team win. Some things that we
can clean up just based on kind of how
we were playing it specifically
offensively in the second half. But um
wanted to be able to be smart, kind of
keep the clock running and so uh love
this team. Um a lot of respect for Coach
BS and and that group and um you know
we'll move on and and start getting
ready for the uh the Panthers.
We did, you know, maybe so, but we ran
it. I knew we were going to only run it.
We weren't going to really put him in
harm's way. And so, um, there was a
possibility of that, but because of the
approach felt like it was kind of going
to be similar, I guess, if you will.
>> Lights out.
>> Gravy on a biscuit. I like that, Nick.
[laughter]
the best you've seen this week thus far?
>> I think they're getting better and
better and I think that's a tremendous
tribute to the to the way that these
guys approach every single week. Um, I
think the the game plans that Coach
Schul and the defensive staff are
putting together to really accentuate
and highlight the the skills of our
guys. I think we're being really
efficient on early downs and earning the
right to be able to get into some of the
different, you know, known pass
situations. But, um, I thought they were
great. Uh, what an unbelievable play. I
mean, there's there's a ton of guys that
I could highlight. the Kobe Durant
continues to show um just making play
after play. Even at the end of the game,
you know, they had a good call on the
screen where we were in a you know,
situation where we were in a pressure
and what a play by kit, you know, to be
able to kind of knife his way through
and make that tackle. But guys came up
big. I thought I felt our rush. Um and
you know, that's a really tough offense.
Hopefully Baker's going to be okay, but
uh really pleased and proud of that
group for sure.
[snorts]
>> It's been awesome. You know, we've
really talked about starting fast,
finishing strong, and you know, when we
get leads like that, you know, you are
kind of playing up against the clock,
but I thought we had total command and
control of the football game in the in
the first half. And then really, it was
about, you know, let's you there was a
couple things that, you know, wanted to
be able to have a little bit better
momentum offensively, but um I got to do
a better job for us collectively, but
man, it's awesome. I love the way these
guys are starting and um you know, we
got to continue that because uh we all
know that humility is only a week or a
day away.
Yeah, I I think it feels like the game's
slowing down. I feel like he's in total
command. I think he's got a lot of trust
in the teammates that he's playing with
and um you know, there's a true
ownership and it's I think he's just
totally and completely present and he's
really just enjoying the opportunity to
compete week in and week out. you know,
even just when he does the breakdown
with the team, he loves being a part of
this team. You can feel that he instills
a belief every time that we go out on
the field. We feel like um good things
are going to happen because he's leading
the way. And so, I think he's getting
more and more comfortable with just the
skilled players. You could really see I
thought that was on display tonight. But
I'm really happy for him. Is a cool stat
that artist gave me. You know, 27
touchdowns in a row without an
interception, tying Tom. Um but he's
playing great and uh we'll just continue
to stay in the moment, but I'm loving
every second of this.
Yeah,
>> just just, you know, repetition being
the mother of learning and those guys
just continuing to work together.
There's a ton. I mean, these are two
great players that are just accumulating
experience in the midst of this season
and they're they've got such, you know,
great football acumen and then they've
got the rare ability to be able to, you
know, it's one thing to understand and
to talk about it, but then they have the
ability to be able to bring it to life
and so it's been special. Um, it was an
awesome job for him to get another two
touchdowns tonight and it's cool to be
able to hit him a little bit deeper on
the uh on the go ball down the right
sideline, you know, on his second one.
But they've been awesome and and really
I think Matthew's been awesome with all
of his skilled players. Uh but
especially Devonte has been cool.
>> NFC.
>> Yeah. The only thing that would matter
is if the season ended right now. So um
you know it's it you know do you
remember who was in first place with six
weeks left last year? Me either. So um
but point I'm making and I appreciate
the question. They've done a great job
through 11 games of putting themselves
in this position. And when you look
around this league, every single week
something inevitably occurs where you're
saying, "I can't believe that happened.
Let's stay humble. Let's stay in the
moment. Let's continue to lean into our
preparation, have the appropriate
urgency, but also the enjoyment. This
team has fun." Um, and good football is
fun. And when you're doing it with good
people that you don't want to let down,
that's really fun. And so, um, want to
continue to have a great week.
Obviously, we got a great opponent that
we're playing that's got a lot of
momentum. Um, I'll be interested to see
how that game goes tomorrow against a
division opponent and then uh, you know,
we'll enjoy this week of preparation and
then hopefully bring it to life when we
uh are in Carolina on Sunday. [snorts]
>> Well, yeah, I I think he's playing I
think he's making great decisions. I
think he's got great rapport with his
skilled players. I think he's seeing the
field really well and and I think he's
understanding where are those times and
places cuz it's not like he's not
putting the ball, you know, in, you
know, we're not pushing the ball or
doing some different things like that,
but I think he's being um incredibly
smart but aggressive and um you know,
it's just like anything else. He's a
fine wine. He's just getting better with
age, but he's playing really well. He's
in total command. Yeah, you like that
one. Um so I think he's going to play
for about 10 more years now. So that's
uh but but no, he's he's doing great. I
I just think what he's he's in command.
I think he's got a lot of trust in his
teammates. I think there's just a good
rapport and we want to keep stacking
them. You know, we've got u you know,
another one this week and uh we'll try
to do a great job of uh you know,
allowing him to continue to play that
way. And I'm I'm really happy for
Matthew.
>> Sean, we talked a lot this week about
the loss of Quick, not what impressed
you the most about the way those guys
handled that situation. Yeah, you know,
McCra ended up getting his groin a
little bit earlier in the game, so he
didn't play as many snaps as maybe we
thought he would. But Josh Wallace, all
he does is just answer the bell. Um,
he's so steady, so reliable. You don't
ever replace a Quinton Lake. I I love,
you know, Q, our our teammate, his
teammates love him, his coaches love
him. Um, but I think there's an
understanding and an appreciation of all
right, let's have great communication
verbally and non-verbally in the noise.
Um, let's not be anything other than who
we are. Uh, but I thought the guys
played really well collectively. It's
the best team sport that there is.
That's what you love so much about
football. Josh did his part tonight, but
I thought our defense as a whole was
outstanding, but you don't ever replace
Q and I know he was cheering his ass off
uh you know, watching these guys as was
Higgby and and it was great to be able
to have Rob here. [snorts]
>> Where you going with this, Gary?
>> Yeah. No, that's a good thing. You know
what we can control is to have a great
week of preparation. You guys know me.
It's the coaching cliche, but it's the
truth. I think our guys have done such a
great job of being totally and
completely present. I love the way we've
responded from some setbacks. I love the
way that we've handled a little bit of
success and um you know, through 11
weeks. I'm proud of them. Now, let's see
what we can do through 12. Uh let's see
how we handle ourselves tomorrow. Let's
continue to stack it. And I'm very
confident that we're going to give
ourselves the best chance to do that
because I'm betting on the people in
that locker room, whether it be our
players or our coaches. And um there's
something to be said about not wanting
to let those people down when you love
them that much. And um I think they're
doing some really cool stuff right now,
but it's through 11 games. We play 17
total and and uh all we can control is
our 13th this week or 12th. See, I can't
even do the math. Right. Week 13.
>> And finally, it is Thanksgiving week. So
if we told you at the beginning of the
year it would take you up to this week
to be thankful and grateful to be in
this spot. I mean what would you say
like hey this is where we
>> Oh man I you know what I was thankful
way before this week. I'm I'm thankful
to be around these people. I'm thankful
there's you know we we talk about a
couple things. You know we talk about
being present being grateful. Man, I
have a lot to be grateful for because of
the people that are in my life. Um and
being able to do something that truly
fulfills you uh day in and day out. And
what a what a great challenge it is.
again this week. But very very thankful
to be a part of this group and being
around a bunch of special people and
it's uh it's what gives your life some
purpose.
>> Thanks guys.
you get.
>> Uh yeah, I did. That was cool. That was
awesome. Um it was a great atmosphere
out there today. Um our fans did a great
job showing up. Obviously, both sides of
the ball gave them something to cheer
about early and often, which was really
cool. Um but they were loud. It was a
tough tough environment, I feel like,
for Tampa, and um we appreciate that.
So, it was great.
were able to do that this year. What
changed?
>> It just execution. You know, we've done
a nice job of executing early in the
game. Um, not every game, but we've done
a nice job of, you know, making sure
that you we're getting into a little bit
of a rhythm early on in games. I think
obviously Sean's doing a great job of
setting us up to go out there and play
well, and then, you know, we've gone out
there and executed.
>> When both sides of the ball start out
that way, how do you how do you feel
that?
>> It's awesome. I mean, I feel like if you
were in the stadium, you felt it. And,
you know, we feel it on the sideline. um
go down there uh you know score and then
obviously uh Lark doing what he does um
getting in the zone which was sweet. So,
um, super fired up. Uh, it was a lot of
fun and and obviously some things we can
clean up in the second half be a little
bit better and all those kind of things.
But an interesting game and and
obviously, you know, a good one how we
started.
27 straight touch.
>> What is it?
>> I'm surrounded by really good players.
Um, you know, I've got uh, you know,
great great receivers, great backs,
great tight ends. All of them are
catching touchdowns and and we're
getting in the end zone and and
obviously I can't do any of that if the
guys up front uh, you know, aren't doing
what they're doing and they're doing a
hell of a job, too. So, um, still plays
I want back and and things that we can
be better on. Um, but, uh, I'm enjoying
playing with this group. It's such a
steady group. Week in and week out. they
show up to work. You know, not every day
is perfect. Um, but, you know, we have
that confidence that, you know, we just
keep putting the work in and the results
will be, you know, what we want them to
be and and, um, it's been a whole lot of
fun. So, I'm just enjoying it.
>> Can you expand on that piece of
confidence? Can you explain your
confidence right now?
>> Yeah, I mean, I feel like I got to go
earn it every single week. You know, I I
get out there um, you know, in practice
and and, uh, you know, try to be as good
as I can. And some days I'm, you know,
I'm better than others. And and uh you
know, I still uh I still kind of live
and die with practices sometimes, you
know, and and um if I have a bad one, it
kind of eats me up for the day. I can't
wait to get back out there. So, um you
know, all that is earned and and it's
never going to be perfect. You're not
going to sit out there and, you know,
throw the ball exactly where you want to
and go and do everything you want to
every single time. But just trying to
always push myself and my teammates to
be as good as we can. And and uh the fun
thing for me is we got a locker room
full of the same kind of guys, you know,
and and uh that just want to, you know,
perform for each other and, you know, be
there for our team and it's so cool when
all these guys are scoring touchdowns
and everybody's pulling for each other.
It's a lot of fun to be a part of.
>> Uh I'm not trying to label it. I just
know I'm having fun and uh you know, my
body feels pretty good um at the moment.
Um, like I said earlier, the guys up
front are doing a hell of a job of
keeping me clean. Sean's got great game
plans week in and week out for us to,
you know, do what we need to do to be
successful on our side of the ball. And,
uh, it's it's been a lot of fun.
Where has that come from?
>> Yeah, that other guy is still there. Um
but uh no, it uh it's a whole lot of
fun. I think you know my situation
during training camp with the injury
that I was going through and and um not
being able to really do much of anything
for about four to six weeks, whatever it
was. you know, sometimes uh being
without something, you know, lets you
know how much you you really uh love
doing it and I love playing this game, I
appreciate it. I thought what Jimmy did
in training camp um with our group was
awesome and the way he kept those guys
rolling and and he played great and kind
of gave us that good momentum going into
it and then I kind of just picked up
where he left off. So, got to give him a
ton of credit for what he was able to do
and and then just
I don't know. I uh when you're without
something like that and and then you get
the chance to go back and do it, um it
sure is a whole lot of fun. And
obviously it's a lot of fun winning ball
games and and um you know helping other
guys get in the end zone.
>> Sean said you're being smart but
aggressive.
>> What's that balance for you to do that
everywhere?
Yeah, I mean I I you know that's a
decision every time the ball's in my
hand. And so I'm trying to do the best I
can at uh you know putting the ball
where it needs to go, not putting in
harm's way, but also not you know taking
chances when when we got opportunities
because we got great skilled players out
there and I got to give those guys
chances. So um I don't know. It's just
something I'm doing trying to do the
best I can. It's never perfect, but uh
just um you know just trying to uh
continue to move the ball down the field
without putting it in harm's way.
uh the go ball. Yeah. Um felt like we
had, you know, one-on-one over there and
safety wasn't really moving over there,
cheating it. So, I just kind of peaked
his release. Know we had a concept kind
of coming to me, uh, you know, on the
backside of it and, uh, he peaked the
release and it was a good one. And, uh,
was able to, uh, put it in a good spot
and, you know, he did the rest. So, he's
uh he's done a hell of a job, you know,
when he's been matched up one-on-one
with guys um winning all sorts of
routes, and it's been a whole lot of fun
getting to getting to throw him the
rock.
>> Today was early. Um you know, sometimes
it takes a minute to get into it. Um but
today felt good. Um I thought Sean did a
hell of a job kind of dialing it up for
us early on and and uh we were able to
go kind of put the pedal to the metal
and then our defense played great. got
us the ball back. Um, you know,
obviously scored for us, so it was uh a
total team effort, but definitely felt
like uh early on our guys were doing a
hell of a job winning on the outside and
I was just trying to give them chances.
>> Thanks.
>> See what I'm saying?
you feel like
>> uh
good momentum shift. Um I give all glory
to God for that. Uh and the defensive
line, the defensive line, man, I got to
give thanks to them, man, because they
making our life easy on the back end. Um
each and every play they on the
quarterback. So, uh you know, just give
thanks when it's due, man. And you know,
as a collective, man, we playing 11 as
one. We just got to keep going.
>> It looked like you physically stole the
ball.
Describe what your mindset was to steal
that
If I want it, I'mma get it.
Feel me? Uh, I seen him bobbling it and
I immediately in my mind I'm like, I'm f
to take this ball. So, uh, yeah. And
then I, you know, I went the distance.
Then I seen I'm like, "Oh, Baker
Mayfield. I can't get tackled by Baker."
[laughter] You feel me? Like I can't get
tackled by Baker. So I kind of slow down
a little bit to let Josh Wallace get in
front of me. And then, you know, with a
good block, man, I go in the end zone,
do the bird walk, and then, you know,
it's all good.
>> What did you think of Matthew?
>> Oh, I ain't even knew he did. That's
awesome. He need to come back in here.
We gota talk about that. You know what
I'm saying? So, uh, that that's good
though, man. Every time I do run out and
they call me out, uh, on the, um, on the
jumbotron, I always see him doing the L
shark thing. So, that that's cool. And I
always tell my mom like, "Mom, Matthew
did the L." [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> You guys talked in practice this week
about, you know, trying to split up the
responsibility.
Like, how do you guys feel like you guys
stepped up and communicated with each
other, kept the momentum going from last
week? biggest thing just having the
communication. Um, you know, day in and
day out, man, talking to the guys that
had to step up in his position, Roger
McCur, uh, Josh Wallace, and, um, you
know, with us being the guys in the
secondary, um, that was the biggest
thing, just communicating with them
because it's kind of like it's new to
them. not really new, but you know, they
don't get as many game reps. And uh for
them to get those game reps, man, to
come in and, you know, pick up where Q
left off, that's amazing.
>> Come on, man. We talked about that
earlier in the week. I told you the word
of the week was stamina. And I said when
I I said, I want you to meet me back in
the locker room after the game after I
catch that peak. What I was going to
say, stamina. [laughter]
[clears throat]
>> So, what's it like being number one in
the in the conference? the Thanksgiving.
>> Oh, I didn't know that. I didn't know we
was number one. I won't be keeping up
with that. But, you know, uh I know that
now. So, uh that's a good feeling.
>> Um we just got to keep stacking these
W's in the column, man, and you know,
taking it one game at a time, man.
That's all I can really say about that.
>> Make your Thanksgiving dinner tastes a
little better.
>> Oh, yeah. A whole lot.
You played a lot of really good people
in your life.
Some of the best you've ever played.
>> Um I mean, yeah, to some degree. Yeah, I
think I think I'm I'm definitely most
importantly I'm having the most fun
playing that I that I've ever had and um
yeah, real grateful for the opportunity
to play for a team like this.
>> What makes this the most fun you've ever
had?
>> Um
it's hard to put your finger exactly on
on what you know what makes it feel like
that, but it's it's just one of those
teams where we just have a lot of fun
together. You know, everybody you can
see the from the the celebrations to the
you know the the intense moments out
there. It's just it's just one of those
things where we just find a way to
really enjoy, you know, being, you know,
Sean's always talking about being
totally and completely present. And
that's really where we are. I mean, it's
it's not really nobody's thinking about
the third quarter. Nobody's thinking
about the end of the game. It's it's
more about just enjoying where where our
feet are and going out and playing, you
know, the biggest team sport that there
is together and and coming out obviously
on top of a lot of these games. Um that
that helps the feeling a lot as well.
How would you describe the way that
>> I mean, he's playing like the most
valuable player in the in the league? I
mean, you you can see it in the the
numbers. Um, the way he's taking command
of the the huddle and and the offense.
Um, you know, the way him and Sean put
things together and and and worked, you
know, throughout the the week together
to put together a good product for us.
Um, just just all around. I mean, he's
he's a great leader and obviously knows
how to put points on the board and and
keep this offense moving.
>> I know, but obviously I want to you were
17 and 12, the best.
>> I mean, I don't that's not going to make
me score next week by you you saying
that, me saying it. I I'll leave it for
you to to comment on that. I won't I
won't comment on that. We we believe in
ourselves and and obviously um you know,
we we've put together a decent body uh
of work this year, but at the end of the
day, just, you know, crowning people the
the best duo, that didn't do anything
for the team. So, um again, I'll I'll
let you guys uh talk about that one.
last year.
>> Um, well, it was a play that wasn't
initially I wasn't number one in the
progression there, but it
[clears throat] just shows why practice
is so valuable and, you know, we had a
similar rep to that in in the week and
and he didn't see me and then we were
looking, you know, we have these video
boards in practice now. So, he looked
over and saw that I I killed the, you
know, similar to to what happened to the
to 27 out there. Um, poor kid. Um,
yeah, it's he just was the one in the
way today and and uh yeah, it wasn't
anything personal. It's just just the
way it got to go.
>> Did you run up to the tunnel after you?
>> Yeah, I made it. I I made it to the 405.
[laughter]
It was it was close. Um, no, it was
Yeah, that it was kind of slippery, so I
just kept going just to slowly, you
know, slow it down. But, uh, yeah, ended
up coming back and we we still got our
sies in and everything. I almost we was
on the field a little long this time,
but we'll speed it up a little bit next
time.
>> Have you seen the old video of Bo
Jackson doing that?
>> I have. Yeah. Yeah. I did my best I did
my best impression. My best uh did my
best Bo Jackson impression. I actually
did that in 2017. We I had a walk-off
against the the Browns on a screen that
I scored and then I actually took it to
the all the way to the uh to the to my
locker room. But that is not where our
locker room is. So that wouldn't have
did me much good on that one. [snorts]
>> Caught passes from MVP. Stafford's got
27 touchdown passes without
interception. As an elite wide receiver,
how do you [snorts] articulate that? How
do you describe?
>> It's It's hard to put it in words. It's
hard to conceptualize the fact that you
can throw put the ball in the end zone
that many I mean, it's hard enough. I
don't most quarterbacks can't throw 27
passes, you know, without throwing a
pick. So, um, to to see him do that and
and come out here and it's not on our
minds. It's not on his mind, you know,
it's it's just the way that that he
plays. And, you know, we we're a pretty
efficient offense. So we we do
everything we can to protect the ball
and uh he does most of the work. So we
just go out there and run try to run
good routes and uh yeah we just let him
put on the money.
>> I know your standards high and last week
you talked after the game about how you
wanted to delete that film. Uh so what
is the feeling like to be able to go out
and flush it?
>> Well, that's just I feel like that's
what good players um good teams are all
about, you know, being able to make
mistakes. this this game is the most
imperfect team game that there is. So,
it's going to be times, you know, time
and time again where you don't produce
the product that you want to put out
there. Um, but how you respond is really
what's most important. So, um, went out
and had a really good week of practice.
I feel like we were flying around. Me
and Matthew were were were hooking up.
You know, the offense looked good. Um,
you know, even through a few, you know,
guys being banged up the way that we
held it together and put together some
good practice in the rain, too. um you
know it kind of not that you can
guarantee anything by the way you
practice but you you could see it in the
way that we went unprepared and you know
the intentionality of this offense um
taking the field every single time you
know every every single period would you
know getting better on our mind so uh we
definitely not in a in a position where
we feel like you know we're good we can
relax we always trying to get better
>> this one and then uh Sam
>> based on that I'm curious how you
experience see that displayed every
>> Well, first he's not actually betting.
That's This is It's dangerous waters
these days. Um Yes. Figuratively
speaking, he was Yeah. I mean, we I love
that he would figuratively uh bet on us
uh all day. It's it's it's something
that obviously he gets to see the way we
work and how much it means to us. So, um
you know, I'm just like he would say
that. I I bet on him, you know, getting
those good calls off the call sheet all
game and putting us in the best spots,
you know, throughout the entirety of the
game as well. Having
played for two of the most [snorts]
devoted fan bases
and the Rams over the last 10 years have
really tried to build up their fan base.
Have you noticed a difference uh this
year? Does this seem like was pretty
solid Rams fans?
>> Well, I can't I can't really speak for
any years past, but I know even
throughout the the season as it's
progressed, I've I've today was the
loudest I've heard the that crowd. So,
um I appreciate it. We need that we need
that type of energy. It was a little
quieter at the end when when everybody
was already probably at home. Um but
it's it's a it's a good feeling knowing
that you know it means a lot to them. Um
you know to have Muki at the game and um
you know some guys last home game um you
know it means a lot to us just see him
show up and and support us. So we try to
go out there. It means a lot for us to
you know give them something to watch
and and something to be proud of as
well.
Yep.
The mic is on. Okay. [laughter]
>> No, absolutely not.
you were able to get a couple sets there
today.
>> Yeah.
>> Um I mean we were really able to get
after the passer. Um I thought that
there were some opportunities last week
that we got after him a little bit. Uh
but where we really needed to finish um
a little bit stronger and uh he was able
to get the ball out a little faster too.
Uh today he held on to the ball a little
bit more and you know when that happens
the rush has to come alive. So cannot be
prouder um of our front. I mean I can't
have two sacks unless the rest of the
guys are doing their job. uh we can't
have, you know, the the individual
success that we have unless the rest of
the team is doing it. So, could not be
prouder of those guys.
>> How would you rate this defense as right
now?
>> I mean, we believe that we're the best
in the world. Um, and that's our
mentality and that's how we approach
everything. Um, and then we go out
throughout the week to make sure that we
put in the preparation that's going to
result in us being the best in the world
as well. So, that's our mentality.
That's our mindset. Um, and that's what
we're chasing. your first two years the
team has had to overcome slow starts as
the year has gone by. What do you think
about the way this team has handled
early season success for the first time?
>> Yeah. Um well, one I think a lot of this
team has carried over from the past two
years and honestly to me it doesn't feel
all that different. Obviously you have a
lot of wins in the win column. Um but
it's the same mentality. I mean the the
way that we're tenacious after just
chasing after wins. It's always about
the next week. I'm not even paying too
much attention to like what our record
is. It's just the next week, how are we
going to figure out a way to go win? And
so, I could not be prouder of these
guys, the way that we continue to attack
success. Um, there is no off week. Uh,
you know, that humble pie is always a
week away. Um, in this league, anybody
can beat you at any point in time. And
so, it's about us continuing to to go
out each and every Sunday and put our
our best out there.
>> Your mind when Kobe Turner got that
interception.
>> Say that again. when Kobe Turner got the
interception was kind of going
>> Oh, when Kobe got that interception. Uh
yeah, that was crazy. It was Kobe
Durant. Um but [laughter] but that was
sick. I mean, I saw him bobbling the
ball and I was like, Kobe's going to
strike him and then he got the ball out
and then he just takes off running. I
took off running and I was like trying
to find a block. Nobody was nearby, so I
didn't block anybody. He was patient,
too. Had a little bit of vision, scored.
Um and then they always run far away as
they can. I mean, he could have like
celebrated right there. He went to the
opposite corner. So I was like, I guess
I'm going um did the celebration with
him and I was out of breath. I was I was
sitting down on the sideline. I was
like, "Please GIF, do not put me back
in." But that was an incredible play,
man. And he's uh he's continued to have
incredible plays um multiple times
honestly this year. So uh just continued
continuing to be proud of him and the
way that he continues to come out and
ball out.
>> You guys have the best record in the
NFC. Mhm.
>> Does that mean that you control your
destiny for the number one?
>> Yeah, I think that's cool. Um, I think
our mentality is still just go out each
and every week and find a way to win.
And I think that's what makes us great,
honestly. Uh, to be able to have the
humility of the past two years and
having to know, you know, when November
comes, it separates the contenders from
the pretenders. And it's about figuring
out a way to go out and pick up another
W. And so, we're not out here looking at
our record and getting caught up in
that. We're just focused on how are we
going to go and pick up the next W. And
I think that's going to continue to take
us far. Um, but yeah, it definitely does
feel nice to be able to pick up as many
wins as we have and uh there's hopefully
a lot more in store.
>> You mentioned mentioned the front of
you. How sweet is it to
honoring today?
>> Yeah, it's special. Um, obviously he
means so much to this organization. He
means so much to this Dline. Um the
fearsome forsome set a foundation. He
continued that legacy. A lot of other
guys have continued that legacy but
obviously him most recently. And so to
be able to pick up where he left off and
to try to be as fearsome as a front as
we can be um to be as fearsome as we can
be as as he was in in one person. So um
it means a lot a special day obviously
my calls my cleat as well. Um, and I was
able to uh support Chera. Um, and that
was a very special opportunity for me as
well. Um, but this so much meaning to
this game and obviously another
opportunity as Sean says to ascend and
we definitely ascended this week and
looking forward to doing it again.
>> How did you come to be played theme
song?
Did you have sheet music?
>> Yeah, so I did uh Chase sent it over to
me, but Thursday night football they
sent me over some sheet music and the
theme song. Um, and it was like 5
minutes long and I was like, "Okay, I'm
going to have to rearrange this."
There's like trumpets and strings and
I'm like, "I'm only doing piano so I
have to rearrange this." Um, so that was
a fun opportunity. And then they came
back with this one, too. So, uh, this
time he just sent the, uh, like the the
voice memo of what the theme song was. I
picked it up by ear. Um, and then I
rearranged it, too, cuz that was another
three minute long song, and I was like,
how can I emulate that within just the
keys and just me, you know, in a solo
take? So, that was a lot of fun. I mean,
obviously I love music. I have a degree
in music as well. Um, and I anytime that
I can learn something new and anytime I
can, you know, flex that music muscle,
uh, is a lot of fun. So, that was a
really great thing to learn on a Friday
night. Did
>> you know they were going to do it?
>> Uh, Chase gave me a heads up and then he
sent it over. I looked at it on Friday
night. Uh, you know, learned it, figured
out how I wanted to arrange it on Friday
night. And then on Saturday in the
morning, I did a take. It was actually,
uh, my first take. And at the end of the
video, I was I got up. I was super
excited. Um, but yeah, I sent that over
and that was that was a ton of fun.
>> Last one, guys.
>> Were there any special moments prior to
the game?
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean, I was able to I was able
to see him when I when I ran out. I saw
him. He was talking with Brockers with
Chris Long. Um, so I was able to stop
by, say hey to him, say hey to his wife.
I told him we were going to go out and
get it done today. Um, and then I ran
off to do my thing. Uh, but so much love
for that guy. Uh, he's a great human
being, obviously a great person. Uh,
obviously a great player. Um, so just
was able to to say hey to them and then
got busy and and did my thing today.
>> Appreciate you guys.